Finding Aid for the George Peabody College Photograph Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Series VII: Campus Events
  - Pershing, General John J. Visit, 1921
  - Phonothon (2)
  - Picnics (13)
  - Pottery Exhibit, 1962
  - Receptions (11)
  - Reflector Composites/Collages (5)
  - Reflector Covers (3)
  - Registration (12)
  - Religious Emphasis Days (4)
  - Roosevelt, President Franklin D. Visit
  - Semi-Centennial Celebration (4)
  - Summer Concerts
  - Teachers College of the Air, 1930-1945 (8)
  - Telethon
  - Town Meeting of the Air, 1950
  - United Daughters of the Confederacy Meeting, 1941
  - Vespers (3)
  - Visitors to Campus (5)
  - Vocational Conferences
  - Watermelon Cutting Day (15)
  - Weddings (2)
- Series VIII: Campus Features
  - Aerial Photographs (4)
  - Aerial Photographs/Maps
  - Animals (2)
  - Antiques
  - Art Collection
  - Athletic Fields
  - Campus Scenes (30)
  - Campus Scenes with People (3)
  - Children (5)
  - Demolition
  - Infirmary
  - Iris Photographs (3)
  - Mall
  - Musical Instruments
  - Offices
  - Smokestack (2)
  - Snow Scenes (37)
  - Snow Scenes with People (17)
  - Tree of Knowledge
  - Victory Garden
- Series IX: Demonstration School
  - Alumni Reunions
  - Athletics (2)
  - Awards
  - Band
  - Christmas Programs (2)
  - Class Projects
  - Classroom Scenes (6)
  - Dutra, President Enrico Gaspar Visit
  - Graduations
  - National Forensic League
  - Physical Education (2)
  - School Events
  - Staff
  - Student Activities (4)
  - Student Groups –Small
  - Student Groups –Large
  - Theater Productions (3)
  - Youth Orchestra (2)
- Series X: Faculty, Administrators, and Staff
  - Administrators –Presidents (6)
  - Administrators (2)
  - Faculty –Activities (6)
  - Faculty –Conference –Gatlinburg, Tennessee 15-17, September 1961 (10)
  - Faculty –Conference –Montgomery Bell Park, Tennessee (3)
  - Faculty –Dinners/Receptions (3)
  - Faculty –Faculty with Students (2)
  - Faculty –Groups –Formal (7)
  - Faculty –Groups –Informal (10)
  - Faculty –Groups –Meetings (4)
  - Faculty –Individuals –Unidentified (3)
  - Faculty –Picnics (4)
  - Faculty –Wives
  - Faculty –Women’s Club
  - Peabody Dames (3)
  - Staff –Activities
  - Staff –Awards Presentations (2)
  - Staff –Cafeteria (2)
  - Staff –Maintenance (5)
  - Staff –Miscellaneous (3)
  - Staff –Office (5)
  - Staff –Police/Traffic Control (2)
  - Staff –Staff Club
  - Tennessee Educators Association
  - Women’s Club
- Series XI: Fraternities
  - Inter-Fraternity Council
  - Alpha Psi Omega
  - Beta Beta Beta (2)
  - Beta Epsilon Kappa
  - Delta Pi Epsilon
  - Gamma Beta Phi
  - Kappa Delta Pi –Activities (2)
  - Kappa Delta Pi –Group Photos (2)
  - Kappa Delta Pi –Officers
  - Kappa Delta Rho
  - Kappa Phi Kappa –Activities
  - Kappa Phi Kappa –Group Photos (2)
  - Kappa Phi Kappa –Officers
  - Phi Chi Alpha –Activities
  - Phi Chi Alpha –Athletics
  - Phi Chi Alpha –Cheerleaders
  - Phi Chi Alpha –Formals
  - Phi Chi Alpha –Group Photos
  - Phi Chi Alpha –Hootenanny Party, 1963
  - Phi Chi Alpha –Meetings (2)
  - Phi Chi Alpha –Officers
  - Phi Chi Alpha –Parties
  - Phi Chi Alpha –Pledges (2)
  - Phi Chi Alpha –Sweethearts
  - Phi Delta Kappa –Activities
  - Phi Delta Kappa –Group Photos (2)
  - Phi Delta Kappa –Officers
  - Phi Delta Theta –Activities
  - Phi Mu Alpha –Activities (2)
  - Phi Mu Alpha –Group Photos (2)
  - Phi Mu Alpha –Sweethearts
  - Pi Gamma Mu –Activities
  - Pi Gamma Mu –Group Photos
  - Pi Gamma Mu –Officers
  - Pi Omega Pi
  - Sigma Alpha Iota –Activities
  - Sigma Alpha Iota –Group Photos (3)
  - Sigma Alpha Iota –Officers
  - Sigma Epsilon –Activities
  - Sigma Epsilon –Athletics (2)
  - Sigma Epsilon –Cheerleaders
  - Sigma Epsilon –Officers
  - Sigma Epsilon –Parties
  - Sigma Epsilon –Pledges
  - Sigma Epsilon –Rush Activities
  - Sigma Epsilon –Sweethearts
- Series XII: Sororities
  - Pan-Hellenic Council (2)
  - Sororities –Sorority Life (5)
  - Beta Kappa Tau –Activities (3)
  - Beta Kappa Tau –Athletics
  - Beta Kappa Tau –Banquets
  - Beta Kappa Tau –Formals (2)
  - Beta Kappa Tau –Group Photos
  - Beta Kappa Tau –Officers (2)
  - Beta Kappa Tau –Parties (2)
  - Beta Kappa Tau –Pledges (2)
  - Beta Kappa Tau –Rush Activities (5)
  - Delta Phi Sigma –Activities
  - Delta Phi Sigma –Athletics
  - Delta Phi Sigma –Banquets
  - Delta Phi Sigma –Formals
  - Delta Phi Sigma –Officers (2)
  - Delta Phi Sigma –Parties
  - Delta Phi Sigma –Pledges
  - Delta Phi Sigma –Rush Activities (6)
  - Delta Rho Beta –Activities
  - Kappa Delta Epsilon –Activities
  - Kappa Delta Epsilon –Group Photos
  - Phi Theta Epsilon –Activities (4)
  - Phi Theta Epsilon –Athletics
  - Phi Theta Epsilon –Officers
  - Phi Theta Epsilon –Pledges
  - Pi Gamma Chi –Activities
  - Pi Gamma Chi –Athletics
  - Pi Gamma Chi –Banquets
  - Pi Gamma Chi –Formals (2)
  - Pi Gamma Chi –Group Photos
  - Pi Gamma Chi –Officers (2)
  - Pi Gamma Chi –Parties (2)
  - Pi Gamma Chi –Pledges (2)
  - Pi Gamma Chi –Rush Parties (4)
  - Pi Gamma Chi –Teas (2)
- Series XIII: Student Activities
  - Banquets (2)
  - Baptist Student Union
  - Biology Club
  - Business Education Council
  - Cafeteria Scenes (6)
  - Camping
  - Campus Capers
  - Campus Crusade for Christ
  - Card Games (2)
  - Carnival
  - Cheerleaders
  - Chemoteers
  - Choir (4)
  - Class Officers
  - Classroom Scenes (14)
  - College Radio
  - Coronation Queen and Ball, 1951-1953
  - Coronation Queen and Ball, 1953-1957
  - Coronation Queen and Ball, 1958
  - Coronation Queen and Ball, 1958-1959
  - Coronation Queen and Ball, 1960 (3)
  - Coronation Queen and Ball, 1961 (2)
  - Coronation Queen and Ball, 1963 (2)
  - Coronation Queen and Ball, 1964
  - Coronation Queen and Ball, 1964-1965
  - Coronation Queen and Ball, 1966-1967, 1969
  - Coronation Queen and Ball, 1970
  - Dance Band
  - Dance Club
  - Dance Groups (8)
  - Dances (9)
  - Dogpatch Day (8)
  - Dorm Life (13)
  - Dorm Life –Confederate Memorial Hall (9)
  - Dorm Life –East Hall (6)
  - Dorm Life –Graduate (North Hall) (12)
  - Dorm Life –West Hall (9)
  - Dramatic Club
  - Elementary Council Club (4)
  - English Club
  - Entrepreneurs Club
  - Fishing Club
  - Football Crowds (2)
  - Foreign Students (12)
  - Freshman Class Officers (3)
  - Freshman Talent Show (2)
  - Fun Night
  - Girls Chapter
  - Girls Chorus
  - Glee Club
  - Graduate Club
  - Groups –Female –Formal Attire –Unidentified (3)
  - Groups –Unidentified (22)
  - Health Club
  - Home Economics Club (4)
  - Homecoming (3)
  - Industrial Arts Club
  - Infirmary
  - Inter-Class Day (2)
  - Inter-Dormitory Council
  - International Club (4)
  - Initiation
  - Intramurals (2)
  - Intramurals –Badminton
  - Intramurals –Basketball (10)
  - Intramurals –Field Hockey (2)
  - Intramurals –Football (9)
  - Intramurals –Golf
  - Intramurals –Kickball
  - Intramurals –Mermaids (10)
  - Intramurals –Ping Pong
  - Intramurals –Soccer (2)
  - Intramurals –Softball (2)
  - Intramurals –Swimming (3)
  - Intramurals –Tennis (4)
  - Intramurals –Volleyball (8)
  - Intramurals –Women’s Basketball (8)
  - Intramurals –Women’s Soccer
  - Intramurals –Women’s Softball
  - Intramurals –Women’s Powder Puff Football (2)
  - Jazz Ensemble
  - Junior Class Officers (2)
  - Library Scenes (7)
  - Library School Club (2)
  - Madrigalians (5)
  - Marching Band (5)
  - Mathematics Club
  - Miss Home Economics (2)
  - Miss United Givers Fund
  - Mr. & Miss Peabody, 1940’s
  - Mr. & Miss Peabody, 1940’s –1957
  - Mr. & Miss Peabody, 1957-1958
  - Mr. & Miss Peabody, 1959 (3)
  - Mr. & Miss Peabody, 1960 (2)
  - Mr. & Miss Peabody, 1961 (5)
  - Mr. & Miss Peabody, 1962
  - Mr. & Miss Peabody, 1963 (3)
  - Mr. & Miss Peabody, 1964 (3)
  - Mr. & Miss Peabody, 1965
  - Mr. & Miss Peabody, 1967, 1972, and undated
  - Music Club
  - Music –Groups (5)
  - Music –Individuals (6)
  - Music –Singing Groups
  - New York City Trip, 1960-1961
  - Newman Club
  - Nurses Club (5)
  - Orchid Ball
  - Outing Club (3)
  - Pan-American Circle
  - Parties (3)
  - Parties –Cookouts (2)
  - Parties –Halloween (2)
  - Parties –Roller Skating (2)
  - Parties –Pajama
  - Parties –Roaring, 1920’s (2)
  - Parties –Western (3)
  - Peabody Band (3)
  - Peabody Orchestra (4)
  - Peabody Pillar (9)
  - Peabody Players (16)
  - Peabody Post (8)
  - Peabody Women’s Chorus
  - Post M. A. Students Executive Council
  - Physical Education Majors Club (3)
  - Playboy Parties
  - Protests
  - Red Cross Volunteers
  - Reflector Staff
  - Religious Services
  - R.O.T.C.
  - Russia Trip, 1973
  - Scholastic Sorority
  - School Administration Club
  - School Leadership Club (2)
  - Senior Class Photographs
  - Senior Class Officers (3)
  - Ski Trip
  - Snack Bar Scenes
  - Sophomore Class Officers
  - Special Education Club
  - Square Dancing (4)
  - State Clubs
  - Student Association
  - Student Christian Association (4)
  - Student Council (3)
  - Student Council –Elections (4)
  - Student Council –Meetings
  - Student Council –Officers (2)
  - Student National Education Association
  - Student Scenes –Off Campus (3)
  - Student Scenes –Outdoors (45)
  - Student Scenes –Miscellaneous (18)
  - Students Who’s Parents Attended Peabody
  - Sunshine Saturday (2)
  - Symphonic Band (3)
  - Twins Who Attended Peabody
  - Variety Galore
  - Veterans Club
  - Westminster Fellowship
  - Wind Ensemble
  - Who’s Who in American Universities (7)
  - Women’s Recreation Association (8)
  - World Affairs Club
  - World Student Service Fund
  - Y.W.C.A.
  - Young Democrats Club
- Series XIV: World War Two
  - Alumni Overseas
  - Cadets (6)
  - Cadets –Band (2)
  - Cadets –Scenes (4)
  - Cadets –Socializing with Co-eds (2)
- Series XV: Nashville/Tennessee
  - Capitol Building
  - President John F. Kennedy –Campaign Stop in Nashville (2)
  - Nashville –Flood of 1926
  - Nashville –Scenes (3)
  - Parthenon
  - Tennessee –Scenes
- Series XVI: Portraits
  - A
    - Abel, Georgie Lee
    - Abernathy, Emily
    - Abernathy, Hardaway S.
    - Adalman, A N.
    - Adams, Carl
    - Adams, Clinton
    - Adams, Vilna
    - Adams, Zaidee Douglas
    - Adams
    - Aden, Sheila
    - Ald, Margaret
    - Alderman, Sara
    - Alexander, Fred
    - Alexander, Martha King
    - Alexander, Thomas
    - Alexander, Wade
    - Allen, Cecil H.
    - Allen, Claudia
    - Allen, Grace
    - Allen, Jack
    - Allison, Annie
    - Allyerg, Victor
    - Almon, Thomas
    - Alprend, Thyle J.
    - Al-Raheen, Ahmed Hasson
    - Alston, Wallace M.
    - Alstetter, M.L.
    - Amonette, William
    - Anchor, Ken
    - Andersen, Ines Elliot
    - Anderson, James
    - Anderson, Kena
    - Anderson, Norma
    - Anderson, Pauline
    - Anderson, Robert H.
    - Andrews, Lula O.
    - Andrews, Mary Frances
    - Ansel, Martin
    - Anthony, R.E.
    - Antos, Joseph
    - Applebaum, Leon
    - Arendell, J.E.
    - Armstrong, Lillian
    - Armstrong, Noble Boyd
    - Arnick, Thomas C.
    - Arnold, Susan Vaughan
    - Artley, A. Sterl
    - Ashby, Lyle
    - Ashcroft, Sam
    - Atkinson, C.
    - Atkinson, William Madison
    - Atkinson, W. R.
    - Auerbach, Robert
    - Aukenbaur
    - Axson, Stockton
  - B
    - Baben, R. E.
    - Bachman, Frank P.
    - Bacigalupo, David L.
    - Bacon, Hollis Phillip
    - Badger, William
    - Bailey, Chester
    - Bailey, Etta Rose
    - Baird, James O.
    - Baker, Elizabeth W.
    - Baker, Frank E.
    - Baker, John
    - Ball, Jack
    - Ball, Thelma
    - Ball
    - Ballen, J. Minton
    - Balls, Jack
    - Bane, Emily
    - Banks, Frazier
    - Banks, John
    - Barbe, Walter B.
    - Barker, Earl P.
    - Barker, Lewis R.
    - Barkley, Esther
    - Barkley, Mabel A.
    - Barnes, Irwin J.
    - Barnes, Kathleen
    - Barnes, T. C.
    - Barnett, Albert
    - Barnett, James Calvin
    - Barr, Gladys
    - Barr, Thomas C.
    - Barron, M.
    - Barton, John W.
    - Bass, W. A.
    - Bassett, Donna Jean Cook
    - Bates, Lucile W.
    - Batey, Mary
    - Batres, Domingo
    - Batsdale, J. A.
    - Batson, Patsy
    - Batza, Eugene
    - Bauch, Jerold
    - Baugh, Mrs.
    - Baugham, Lloyd E.
    - Baumbach, Carl
    - Beadle
    - Beard, Martha Ruth
    - Beasley, Sarah
    - Beasley, Wallace
    - Beauchamp, Robert
    - Beaver, Eloise
    - Beck, E. C.
    - Beck, Oscar A.
    - Becker, Lawrence
    - Beckett, Lamarah
    - Becton, Emma
    - Beeler, Frances Elizabeth
    - Behm, Euline
    - Behrues, Minnie S.
    - Bek, Chang Moon
    - Beliles, Bill
    - Bell, Phillip
    - Bell, Wayne H.
    - Bellis, Anne
    - Bender, Richard N.
    - Benedict, A. B.
    - Beninger, Suzanne
    - Benjamin, Harold
    - Bennett, Barbara L.
    - Bennett, Eunice Ercelle
    - Benny, Carolina
    - Benny, John E.
    - Bentley, Imogene
    - Benton, John K.
    - Berndt, Mrs. Rex
    - Berry, Betty
    - Berryhill, M. E.
    - Best, Dayle
    - Best, Ellenore
    - Biddle, Frances J.
    - Bigelow
    - Bills, Edith
    - Binkley, Martha
    - Binnion, R. B.
    - Bird, Dick
    - Bird, Linda
    - Birdwell, A. W.
    - Bishop, Eugene L.
    - Bixler
    - Bjork, Robert
    - Black, Ken
    - Blackburn, Clifford
    - Blackburn, Kenneth
    - Blackman, Albert Morris
    - Blackwelder, Harry J.
    - Blanchard, Frank Le Roy
    - Blanding, J. D.
    - Blanding Sarah Gibson
    - Blankenship, A. S.
    - Blanton, Ray
    - Bledsoe, J. M.
    - Bledsoe, Joseph C.
    - Blocker, Lera
    - Blond, Yvonne Irene
    - Blum, Elanor
    - Bobo, James R.
    - Bode, Boyd H.
    - Bodie, Sylvia
    - Boen, C. C.
    - Bogen, Jules I.
    - Boggs, Earl R.
    - Boles, Leo
    - Bolton, Euri Belle
    - Bolton, Frank
    - Bond, Gary
    - Bond, John B.
    - Bond William F. (2)
    - Bonner, Troy M.
    - Bontemps, Arna
    - Booker, Ted W.
    - Boots, Wilson T.
    - Boots, Mrs. Wilson T.
    - Borgeault, Stanley E.
    - Boswell, George
    - Boswell, Mildred
    - Bottari, Flores Tina
    - Bottoms, Mollie Ruth
    - Boult, Reber
    - Bourner, Howard
    - Boushall, Thomas C.
    - Bowen, Blanche
    - Bowman, George Yancey
    - Bowman, M. P.
    - Boyd, Elizabeth Cherry
    - Boyd, Theodore E.
    - Boynton, Paul
    - Bracken, John L.
    - Bradfield, Luther E.
    - Bradford, A. L.
    - Bradford, J. C.
    - Brady, Janice Faye
    - Bramblett, Anne
    - Bramley, Aileen Wade
    - Brandon, J.
    - Brandon, Willard
    - Brantley, Rabun L.
    - Brasfield, S. A.
    - Braswell, James S., III.
    - Bravo, Cesar
    - Bridges, D. W.
    - Briley, Beverly
    - Brinkley, Vicky
    - Brisby, Herbert
    - Brister, J. W.
    - Bristow, Gilbert J.
    - Broadwell, Martin M.
    - Brock, Claude E.
    - Brockman, Fletcher S.
    - Brogdon, Mary C.
    - Brooks, B. P.
    - Brooks, Hall
    - Brooks, Harley
    - Brooks, Margaret E.
    - Brouillette, J. W.
    - Brouillette, Jean Martha
    - Brown, Bettye
    - Brown, Bill
    - Brown, Clyde
    - Brown, Helen
    - Brown, Ida Lee
    - Brown, John Mason
    - Brown, Luther Daniel
    - Brown, Nancy
    - Brown, R. H.
    - Brown, W. M.
    - Brown, Wilma
    - Brownell, William A.
    - Bruce, Charles
    - Bryan, Beatrice Irene
    - Bryan, Charles F.
    - Bryan, Irene
    - Bryant, Hayden
    - Buchanan, Pearl
    - Buckey, Nellie
    - Budewig, Flossie Caroline
    - Buffington, R. M.
    - Buktenica, Norman
    - Bullington, J. R.
    - Bumbrabough, Robert Thomas
    - Bunger, Fred A.
    - Buntin, Rogers C.
    - Burdette, T. L.
    - Burdick, A. E.
    - Burgart, Herbert
    - Burgess, Hewit
    - Burgess, Robert S., Jr.
    - Burk, J. E.
    - Burke, Albert E.
    - Burnett, Belle
    - Burris, George
    - Burrough, Margaret
    - Burrough, Morris P.
    - Burrum
    - Burrus, Mary Helen
    - Burton, M. Alice
    - Burton, Virginia
    - Butcher, Elsa
    - Butler, Suda East
    - Buttrick, George A.
    - Buttrick, Wallace
    - Byerly, Carl A.
    - Byers, Burton H.
    - Byers
    - Byrd, James
  - C
    - Cagle, Frances Catherine Jones
    - Cahoon, Barbara
    - Cain, Duane Vieux
    - Cain, Nellie Jo
    - Cain Robert L., Jr.
    - Calhoun, William J.
    - Calkins, Robert D.
    - Camp, James W.
    - Camp, Mary Evelyn
    - Campbell, Boyd
    - Campbell, Carl G.
    - Campbell, Doak S.
    - Campbell, Mrs. Doak S.
    - Campbell, Marie
    - Cantrall, C.
    - Cantrell, Bettye S.
    - Cardwell, Jesse F.
    - Cardwell, Mildred
    - Carlton, Ralph Kimball
    - Carmen, James T.
    - Carmen, Janelle
    - Carmichael, Benjamin E
    - Carmichael, O. C.
    - Carnegie, Andrew
    - Carney, Grover Cleveland
    - Carney, N. L.
    - Carothers, Betsy
    - Carothers, M. W.
    - Carpenter, W. W.
    - Carr, Edwin R.
    - Carr, Ida
    - Carr, Nancy
    - Carr, William G.
    - Carrillo, Cely
    - Carrington, F. P.
    - Carroll, Paul F.
    - Carson
    - Carter, Clyde Gregory
    - Carter, Ellis Ray
    - Carter, Fannie Mae
    - Carter, Hodding
    - Carter, Lily Purcell
    - Carter, Randolph Laurie
    - Carter, Robert L.
    - Cartwright, Benjamin A.
    - Cartwright, Thomas Blount
    - Cassel, David
    - Cassel, Don
    - Cassel, Walter
    - Caswell, Hollis L.
    - Causey, J. P.
    - Cavanaugh, Roberta Little
    - Cavert, Corrine
    - Celaurd, Francis L.
    - Center, Stella S.
    - Center, William R.
    - Cerf, Bennett
    - Chadwick, William S., Jr.
    - Chamberlain, Faye
    - Chambers, James A.
    - Chamlee, Martha
    - Champion, Grace
    - Chancey, Geneva
    - Chandler, Olive
    - Chandler, Virginia
    - Cheap, Eugenia
    - Cheek, John
    - Cheek, Norman
    - Cheek, Terry
    - Chen, Fu-Hsin
    - Chenault, Bob
    - Cheney, Mary
    - Cheros, Margaret
    - Cherry, H. H.
    - Cherry, Ralph W.
    - Chittum, E. W.
    - Christy, O. B.
    - Chua, Cheng
    - Ciardi, John
    - Clark, Deloris
    - Clark, Ed
    - Clark, Harry
    - Clark, Peggy
    - Clark, Violet D.
    - Claunch, John M. (3)
    - Claunch, Mrs. John H.
    - Clay, Carrie Law
    - Clay, Thomas L.
    - Claypool, Juliana
    - Clayton, Maryella
    - Clement, Frank G
    - Clemons, S. P.
    - Cline, Rodney
    - Clouse, R. Wilburn
    - Clovis, Barbara
    - Cobb, J. E.
    - Cobb, Mary Ann
    - Coble, Mrs. J. C.
    - Coe, Christine Sadler
    - Coe, Fred
    - Coffin, Henry Sloane
    - Cohen, Mrs. Meyer
    - Colhoun, Billy
    - Cole, Ed
    - Cole, Marshall
    - Collier, Clarence B.
    - Collier, Lois
    - Coleman, Hubert
    - Coleman, J. T.
    - Coleman, Mrs. James
    - Collins, Carvel
    - Collins, Earl A.
    - Collins, Genevieve
    - Collins, Maud
    - Collins, Nina
    - Comp, Ralph
    - Compton, Cromwell Dennis
    - Compton, J. W.
    - Conant, Howard
    - Conant, James B.
    - Conger, John J.
    - Conyers, Pearl H.
    - Conyngton, H. J.
    - Cook, Arthur
    - Cook, Ella
    - Cook, JoAnn
    - Cooke
    - Cooper, Claire
    - Cooper, Ken
    - Cooper, Russell M.
    - Cooper
    - Cope, James R.
    - Cope, Quill
    - Copeland, Donna
    - Copeland, J. Isaac
    - Corbett, H. D.
    - Corry, Mabel H.
    - Couch, Harvey C.
    - Couch, Orrie A.
    - Coulling, Martha
    - Counts, George S.
    - Cousins, Norman
    - Cowdrick, Regina C.
    - Cowthon, N. S.
    - Cox, James F.
    - Cox, Lois
    - Coyle, Mrs. James C.
    - Crabb, Alfred Leland
    - Crader, E. Earl
    - Craft Charles
    - Craig, Hardin
    - Craig, Mr. & Mrs. Philip L.
    - Craig, V. W.
    - Cram
    - Crawford, Barbara
    - Crawford, Leonidas W.
    - Crawford, Meredith
    - Crenshaw, Hazel
    - Crisp, Jean
    - Crook, C.
    - Croslin, Kenneth
    - Croslin, Olive June S.
    - Crow, Orin F.
    - Crowe, E. R.
    - Crowley, Dorothy
    - Crowley, W. Bruce
    - Crugh, W. W.
    - Crutcher, Lucile
    - Crutchfield, Susan
    - Cuff, R. P.
    - Cullop, Margaret
    - Cumberworth, Starling
    - Cummings, Charles L.
    - Cummings, Howard H.
    - Cundiff
    - Cunninggim, Jesse L.
    - Cunninggim, Merriman
    - Cunningham, Edna
    - Cunningham, Vicci
    - Curry, Walter Clyde
  - D
    - Dabney, Virginius
    - Dale, Edward Everett
    - Dale, Irwin
    - Dance, Mildred
    - Daniel, Jean
    - Danner, Linnie
    - Dansby, LaMarr
    - Darnell, W. L.
    - David, Lucille
    - Davidson, Donald
    - Davidson, Dorothy
    - Davidson, Love B.
    - Davidson, Nelle C.
    - Davis, Agnes
    - Davis, Alice
    - Davis, Billie
    - Davis, C. W.
    - Davis, Dave
    - Davis, E. A.
    - Davis, Frederick
    - Davis, Hubert J.
    - Davis, Jackson W.
    - Davis, Marjorie
    - Davis, Mary Frances
    - Davis, O. L., Jr.
    - Davis, Robert
    - Dawson, Alice E.
    - Dawson, Howard
    - Dawson, John F.
    - Dawson, Roy E.
    - Dawson, Shelton Phelps
    - Day, J. A.
    - Dean, Nell
    - Deer, George Harris
    - DeLoach, W. S.
    - DeLorre, Lois Nelson
    - Dement, Ann
    - Demiaskevich, Michael
    - DeMoss, Earline
    - Denham, Margaret
    - Denison, Maggie
    - Dennard, E. N.
    - Denton, Bill
    - DePew, Rex
    - DePriest, Frank
    - Derrick, C. P.
    - Derthick, Lawrence G.
    - DeWitt, R. T.
    - Dhar, Ivey Satavati
    - Dickey, Frank G.
    - Dickson, C. Alicia
    - Dickinson, J. M.
    - Didcoct, Betty
    - Didcoct, John J.
    - Dideban, Zahra
    - Dietz, Louise
    - Dildy, Sena
    - Dilla, Geraldine P.
    - Dillion, Frances
    - Dilworth, Bernice
    - DiPietro, Alphonso
    - Dockstader, Frederick
    - Dodd, William E.
    - Dodson, K. Harlan
    - Dodson, Wesley
    - Doggett, Joe
    - Dohnanyi, Ernst von
    - Dokecki, Paul
    - Donahue, Peggy
    - Donehoo, C. A.
    - Donovan, Bernard
    - Donovan, Herman
    - Donovan, Lillian
    - Dorris, Martha E.
    - Dorsey, Julian
    - Dorsey, Julius
    - Doscher, John W.
    - Doss, Mrs. N. B.
    - Dosset, Bungin
    - Dotson, John A.
    - Douglas
    - Dowd, Ben
    - Dowlen, Louise
    - Dozier, Nancy
    - Dozier, Tatum
    - Drake, Richard M.
    - Dresslar, Fletcher Bascom
    - Dresslar, Mrs. Fletcher Bascom
    - Driftwood, Jimmy
    - Drowota, Frank F.
    - DuBerry, Jane Byad Potts
    - DuBose, Rebecca
    - Duggan, Dorothy
    - Dugger, Mary Helen
    - Duke, Anne S.
    - Duke, John
    - Duncan, Eugene
    - Duncan, Ruth
    - Dunham, Franklin
    - Dunlap, Emma
    - Dunkerley
    - Dunn, Betty
    - Dunn, Ruth
    - Dunn, Winfield
    - Dunworth, John
    - Durrant, Vance Posey
    - Durman, Clifford
    - Durrett, Dan
    - Dusen
    - Dutch, George S.
    - Dwight, Leslie A.
    - Dyck, Delbert A.
    - Dyer, John Percy
  - E
    - Eagles, Eulia B
    - Eason
    - Easterly, Daniel Arthur
    - Eckles, W. G.
    - Edmiston
    - Edmonds, Henry M.
    - Edwards, Sidney William
    - Egbert, George
    - Eifer, Sue Ellen
    - Elicker, Paul E.
    - Elkins, Margaret Louise
    - Ellington, Buford
    - Elliot, E. C.
    - Elliot, Willie
    - Ellis, Joyce
    - Ellis, Paul R.
    - Ellis, Zora
    - Ellison, Eula
    - Elsea, A. F.
    - Emmons, S. R.
    - Endicott, Lou
    - Engel, Mary Susan
    - England, L. Kenneth
    - English, Mildred
    - Epstein, Mary
    - Erwin, Clyde
    - Escue, June
    - Estes, Mary Ann
    - Etheridge, Ruby
    - Etzler, Caroline Houts
    - Eubank, Marie
    - Eubank, S.
    - Evans, Forrest F.
    - Evans, H. B.
    - Evans, Luther Harris
    - Evans, Mary Ellen
    - Ewing, Betsy Kenrick
    - Ewing, J. M.
  - F
    - Fain, Eugene
    - Fajardo, Jose
    - Fallis, Charles L.
    - Falls, J. D.
    - Fant, Norman
    - Farley, Gene Clark
    - Farrell, Emma Lucille
    - Farris, Frank
    - Favrot, Leo M.
    - Feaster, Henry Jacob
    - Featherstone, Alta
    - Fenner, Mildred Sandison
    - Fensterwald, Emily
    - Ferguson, Arthur C.
    - Ferguson, Joe
    - Ferguson, Sarah
    - Ferguson, W. C.
    - Ferrell, Guy V.
    - Ferrell, Lexie
    - Fesmiro, Ruth
    - Fields, Freta
    - Fillebrown, T. Scott, Jr.
    - Finch, James T.
    - Fine, Benjamin
    - Fink, Georgia
    - Fink, T. Ross
    - Finley, Mildred